<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ember CSI</title>
    <link>https://ember-csi.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ember CSI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 17:05:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ember-csi.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinder-CSI vs Ember-CSI</title>
      <link>https://ember-csi.io/post/cinder_csi-ember_csi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 17:05:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ember-csi.io/post/cinder_csi-ember_csi/</guid>
      <description>Once people see that Ember-CSI uses the Cinder drivers, they immediately wonder what&amp;rsquo;s the difference between the two CSI plugins, but there is no document that answers that question. They can dig into the documentations of both projects to understand their architectures and come up with the answer, but it&amp;rsquo;s somewhat painful.
In this article we aim to answer the most common questions that will come up when looking into Cinder supported drivers and how to connect them to Kubernetes and OpenShift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driver validation</title>
      <link>https://ember-csi.io/post/validation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 11:13:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ember-csi.io/post/validation/</guid>
      <description>The Ember-CSI team is frequently asked about the supported backends and how to test Ember-CSI with a specific one. In some cases the answer is straightforward, in other cases it&amp;rsquo;s considerably more complex, so we thought it would be a good idea to write an article with all this knowledge, including a step by step guide on how we can validate that a backend works with Ember-CSI.
For the final validation we will be using Ember-CSI&amp;rsquo;s Kubernetes example to deploy a 3 nodes Kubernetes cluster with 1 infrastructure node a 2 workload nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>