<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getstarteds on Ember CSI</title>
    <link>/getstarted/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getstarteds on Ember CSI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/getstarted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenShift 4.x and Ember CSI</title>
      <link>/getstarted/openshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getstarted/openshift/</guid>
      <description>Deploying CSI plugins is a non trivial task, and for Ember-CSI this installation would be even more complex, since there are many supported backends we need to find out what are the right configuration options for ours before we can do the deployment.
In Kubernetes installation is usually done using manifests or Helm charts, but for OpenShift clusters CSI plugins can have their own operator to facilitate the installation process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes and Ember CSI</title>
      <link>/getstarted/k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 19:05:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getstarted/k8s/</guid>
      <description>Many things need to be considered when deploying a CSI plugin in Kubernetes, making it a painful experience for many first time users. To ease this first contact with Kubernetes and CSI, the Ember repository comes with a Kubernetes example that automates the deployment of Kubernetes with Ember CSI using CSI spec version 1.0.
This article covers how to run Ember-CSI as a CSI v1 plugin deployed in Kubernetes 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KubeVirt and Ember-CSI</title>
      <link>/getstarted/kubevirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 19:05:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getstarted/kubevirt/</guid>
      <description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. It allows users to run VMs alongside containers in the their Kubernetes or OpenShift clusters. This document describes a quick way to deploy either Kubernetes or OpenShift, KubeVirt and Ember-CSI.
The Ember-CSI-KubeVirt repository provides a seamless wrapper integrating the deployments of OpenShift or Kubernetes, KubeVirt, Containerized Data Importer (CDI), Ember-CSI and a Ceph demo cluster.
Ember-CSI should always be deployed using the Ember-CSI-Operator, like we do here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>